ragnarok-guide.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy Policy | Ragnarok Guide

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for ragnarok-guide.com and the [Ragnarok Guide](http://www.ragnarok-guide.com/) app. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.

The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.

How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Information Collection, Use, and Sharing 

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new [products](http://www.ragnarok-guide.com/ro/products/) or services, or changes to this [privacy policy](http://www.ragnarok-guide.com/advertise/privacy-policy/).

Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

See what data we have about you, if any.  
Change/correct any data we have about you.  
Have us delete any data we have about you.  
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

## Cookies

We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

We may use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

This site may contain links to other web sites and files. We have no control over the content and can not ensure it will not be offensive. We will remove links to material that we feel is inappropriate as we become aware of them.

## Google Advertising Cookie and Privacy Policies

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.

* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.

* Users may opt out of the use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

## Sharing

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

## Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via this contact form:
